Finding Aid for A. Alfred Taubman papers, 1942-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Shopping Centers/Commercial Development 1956-2009
  - Shopping Center Scrapbooks Photo Albums, Architects' Proposals, and Miscellaneous Reports
    - Farahzad, Iran/Regional Commercial Complex/Joint Venture-TCO. Starrett S.A. January 1975 (Box 43)
    - Hoyt-Schermerhorn -- Mezzanine -- A Proposal (Box 43)
    - Lafayette Place, Boston/I.M. Pei & Partners/Gladstone Associates (Box 43)
    - John Graham & Co. Architects Portfolio of Projects (Box 43)
    - Frank B. Hall & Co., Board of Directors Binder (Box 43)
    - Detroit Department of Defense Facility Proposal 1992 (Box 43)
  - 712 Fifth Avenue
    - Correspondence and Memoranda 1992 (Box 44)
    - Management and Leasing Agreement (Box 44)
    - Agreement of Limited Partnership of: Taubman 56th Street Associates Limited Partnership; T-712 Associates Limited Partnership (Box 44)
    - Taubman Fifth Avenue Associates Limited Partnership Agreement (Box 44)
    - Acquisition of Partnership Interest in Connection with Development of Property at 56th Street and Fifth Avenue, New York, New York February 7, 1986, 5 volumes (Box 44)
    - Master Interest Rate Agreement Protection Agreement April 12, 1991 (Box 44)
    - Amended & Restated Building Loan Mortgage, Revolving Credit Agreements April 1, 1993 (Box 44)
    - Henri Bendel. Inc. Lease and Draft, 2 volumes (Box 45)
    - Various Executed Documents (re Bendel Lease) (Box 45)
    - Debt Restructuring, 1 volumes (Box 45)
    - Building Loan Agreement, 1 volumes (Box 45)
    - Modification of CREI Loan Documents for Second Modification of Henri Bendel Lease Agreement, 1 volumes (Box 45)
    - Brochures, 3 folders (Box 46)
    - Broker's Reception 1991 (Box 46)
    - Correspondence 1991-1998 (Box 46)
    - Logos (Box 46)
    - Magazine (712 West Fifth Avenue)
      - General (Box 46)
      - Congratulation Letters (Box 46)
      - Magazine Distribution (Box 46)
      - Requests (Box 46)
      - Copy, Vol. 1, No. 1 (Box 46)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - New York Times (Paul Goldberger article) (Box 46)
    - Newsletter 1995-1996, 4 folders (Box 46)
    - Weatherall, Green Advertising (Box 46)
  - 795 Fifth Avenue Corporation (Pierre Hotel)
    - 1988-1993, 3 folders (Box 46)
    - Annual Report (Box 47)
    - Legal (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 47)
    - Proprietary Lease (Box 47)
    - Restructuring of Pierre, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Stockholder Information, 3 folders (Box 47)
  - Charleston Center
    - Deferral of UDAG Loan Agreements August 29, 1991, October 29, 1991, 3 volumes (Box 48)
    - Admission of Sea Containers & Conversion to LLC October 6, 1995, 3 volumes (Box 48)
  - Other real estate material
    - Perpetual Preferred Stock Notes 1997 (Box 49)
    - Stoneridge Mall Financing Hypo Bank Closing Book September 26, 1990, 2 volumes (Box 49)
    - Taubman Centers, Inc. Road Show Presentation November 10, 1992 (Box 49)
    - Taubman Centers, Inc. Annual Report 2009 (Box 49)
    - Taubman Realty Group
      - Medium Term Notes, General Information 1995-1996 (Box 49)
      - Private Debt Morgan Stanley September 27, 1993 (Box 49)
      - Prospectus, Floating Rate Notes October 28, 1994 (Box 49)
    - Simon Property Group
      (take-over attempt of Taubman Centers, Inc.)
      - General (Box 50)
      - Proxies (Box 50)
      - TCI SEC filings (Box 50)
      - Articles (Box 50)
  - Visual Materials
    Digital visual materials (1.0 GB) includes images and documentation on various Taubman Company events and shopping centers, as well as related materials on A. Alfred Taubman and other development projects.
    - Detroit Renaissance, circa 1980, .ZIP file
    - Shopping Centers
      - Set 1 1953-2012, .ZIP file
        - Beverly Center, City Creek 1982
        - Columbus City Center 1989
        - Eastridge and Arborland 1970, 1961
        - Fairlane 1976
        - Hilltop 1976, 2007
        - Lakeforest 1978
        - Lakeside 1976
        - Marley Station,1987
        - Meadowood undated
        - North Flint Plaza 1953
        - Northridge 1972
        - Partridge Creek 2005
      - Set 2 1961-2008, .ZIP file
        - Arborland 1961
        - Short Hills 1980-2008
        - Southland, circa 1960s-1972
        - Southridge 1970
        - Stoneridge 2004
        - Sunvalley 1966-1984
        - Twelve Oaks 2008-2009
        - Woodfield 1971-1972
        - Woodland 1968
    - Taubman Company events and anniversaries 1992-2010, .ZIP files)
      - Going public 1992
      - 50th Anniversary 2000
      - 60th Anniversary 2010
    - Miscellaneous 1950s-1990s, .ZIP file
      - Irvine 1977
      - Speedway 1960s
      - Various photographs, clippings, and other documents, circa 1950s-1990s
- Industry Leadership 1972-1998
  The Industry Leadership series documents Taubman's service on the boards of national real estate industry organizations. National Reality Committee records consist of board of directors files from 1972 to 1989. These files include meeting minutes, correspondence, and policy memoranda. Urban Land Institute records include notes and agendas for board of directors' meetings, 1977-1986, and copies of speeches given by Taubman at a number of the organization's meetings.
  - National Realty Committee
    - Board of Directors' Files
      - 1972-1974, 5 folders
      - 1974-1977, 9 folders (Box 51)
      - 1978, 1980-1989, 1998, 12 folders (Box 52)
  - Urban Land Institute
    - 50th Anniversary 1984-1985 (Box 53)
    - Chronological Files
      - 1972-1977, 3 folders (Box 53)
      - 1978 (Box 53)
      - 1981, 5 folders (Box 53)
      - 1982, 2 folders (Box 53)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 53)
      - 1986 (Box 53)
    - Council on Development Choices 1980, 2 folders (Box 53)
    - Meetings
      - Detroit Meeting 1977 (Box 54)
        (includes AAT speech relating to the Irvine land purchase)
      - San Francisco Meeting 1978 (Box 54)
      - Spring Meeting (Texas) 1979 (Box 54)
      - Honolulu Meeting 1980 (Box 54)
      - Miami Meeting
        - Commercial and Retail Development Council 1983 (Box 54)
        - General 1983, 2 folders (Box 54)
        - Reports 1983 (Box 54)
      - Phoenix Meeting 1985 (Box 54)
      - 1986, 3 folders (Box 54)
    - Reports and Studies (Box 54)
    - Remarks 1985-1991, 4 folders (Box 54)
- Detroit Development 1971-1997
  The Detroit Development series documents the contributions Taubman has made to the economic and physical revitalization of Detroit and to the cultural life of the city. There is a small set of records related to Taubman and Max Fisher's development of the Riverfront West condominiums; these include architectural plans, correspondence, and clippings. Additional records relating to Taubman's real estate investments and development of properties in the Detroit area can be found in the Topical series.
  Taubman's work with Detroit Renaissance is documented through agendas and minutes of the board of directors and the Development Projects Committee; financial statements; and files related to the development of the Renaissance Center, Cadillac Center, the theater district, and other projects. There are also board of directors' agendas, meeting minutes, reports, and correspondence of the Economic Growth Council of Detroit (1976-1979) and its successor organization, the Detroit Economic Growth Corporation (1980-1985); and proposals, reports, and correspondence related to Taubman's work on the Michigan Gaming Commission. Finally, the series includes records of Taubman's long service to the City of Detroit Arts Commission and his work on behalf of the Detroit Institute of the Arts, including his membership in the Founder's Society.
  - Detroit Renaissance
    - Board of Directors Meetings 1972-1979, 22 folders (Box 55)
    - Board of Directors Meetings 1979-1981, 11 folders (Box 56)
    - Financial Statements 1979-1983, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Board of Directors Correspondence 1975, 1980-1994, 8 folders (Box 56)
    - Development Projects (Box 57)
    - Development Projects Committee 1986-1991 (Box 57)
    - Grand Circus Project 1988 (Box 57)
    - Information Packet 1979 (Box 57)
    - Long Range Planning Committee 1985-1989 (Box 57)
    - Theatre District Development 1986 (Box 57)
    - "Town Within a City" Project 1988-1990 (Box 57)
    - Detroit Cadillac Center Development Plan (Box 57)
    - Detroit Renaissance Center
      - Construction (Box 57)
      - Correspondence (Box 57)
      - Downtown Detroit Economic Conditions (Box 57)
        (includes Urban Action Partnership)
      - Leasing (Box 57)
      - Leasing Plan (Box 57)
      - News Articles (Box 57)
      - Opening (Box 58)
      - Progress Reports (Box 58)
      - Publications (Box 58)
      - Standard Club: Plans/Drawings, Progress Reports, Opening, 2 folders (Box 58)
      - Tenants, Prospective and Existing (Box 58)
      - Tenant Status Reports (Box 58)
      - Traffic (Box 58)
      - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Riverfront and Downtown Development
    - Revitalization, General 1977-1978 (Box 59)
    - Woodward Avenue Mall (J. L. Hudson) 1978-1979 (Box 59)
    - Riverfront West (and earlier International Towers concept)
      - Engineering Evaluation 1974 (Box 59)
      - General 1971-1981, 6 folders (Box 59)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 59)
      - Riverfront West Hotel (Box 59)
      - Architectural Plans (Box 59)
    - Riverfront / Riverfront Associates (Box 60)
    - Riverfront Projects (Box 60)
    - Washington Blvd. (Box 60)
    - Pennsylvania Station, Riverfront Property (Box 60)
  - Economic Growth Council of Detroit
    - Board of Directors Agendas 1976-1979, 4 folders (Box 61)
    - Board of Directors Records 1976-1979, 3 folders (Box 61)
    - Correspondence 1976-1978 (Box 61)
    - Detroit Economic Development, Published Reports (Box 61)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 61)
  - Detroit Economic Growth Corporation
    - Board Agendas and Related Material 1980-1985 (Box 62)
  - Michigan Gaming Commission
    - Appointment Letter and Executive Order 1994 (Box 63)
    - Casinos, Volume I 1995
      - Correspondence (Box 63)
      - Meeting Notices and Information (Box 63)
      - Newspaper Articles (Box 63)
    - Casinos, Volume II 1995
      - Proposals (Box 63)
      - Information Booklets (Box 63)
    - Casinos, Volume III 1995
      - Proposals
        - Romulus Gaming (Box 64)
        - Foxtown Casino Project (Box 64)
        - Xanadu (Box 64)
        - Harrah's (Box 64)
        - Mirage Resorts, includes video (Box 64)
    - Casinos, Volume IV 1995
      - Proposals
        - Master Plan/City of Detroit (Box 64)
        - Detroit Rescue Mission Ministries (Box 64)
        - Michigan Horse Racing (Box 64)
        - Chippewa Phoenix Casino (Box 64)
        - Video Lottery (Box 64)
    - Economic Impact Subcommittee 1995 (Box 64)
    - Final Report 1995 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence 1997 (Box 64)
  - Detroit Institute of the Arts
    - Arts Commission (Box 65)
    - Centennial Priority Report 1982 (Box 65)
    - Correspondence 1980-1984 (Box 65)
    - Founders Society (Box 65)
    - Joint Improvement/Renovation Committee (Box 65)
    - Planning Committee (Box 65)
    - Agreements 1989 (Box 66)
    - Annual Reports 1985, 1989, 1990, 1994 (Box 66)
    - Arts Commission Meeting 1980, 1985-1994, 15 folders (Box 66)
    - Building Committee Meeting 1988-1993, 4 folders (Box 66)
    - Building Proposals 1988, 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Business Plan 1992-1997 (Box 67)
    - Clippings (Box 67)
    - Committee Lists (Box 67)
    - Correspondence & Memos 1985-1993, 8 folders (Box 67)
    - Detroit Renaissance 1987-1993 (Box 67)
    - Exhibition Planning Calendar (Box 67)
    - Facility Audit (Box 67)
    - Ferri, Roger, Architect (Box 67)
    - Ford Motor Company (Box 67)
    - Founders Society
      - Awards (Box 67)
      - Board of Trustees 1985-1991 (Box 67)
    - Joint Improvement/Renovation Committee 1986-1987 (Box 67)
    - Master Plan 1990 (Box 67)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 67)
    - Outstate Programs 1985-1989 (Box 67)
    - Planning & Policy Committee Meeting 1987-1993, 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Press Releases 1991 (Box 67)
    - Printed (Box 67)
    - Search Committee 1985-1990 (Box 67)
    - Stabilization Fund 1992, 1994 (Box 67)
    - Staff Directory (Box 67)
    - Strategic Plan 1983, 1988-1989, 5 folders (Box 67)
- Business Investments 1968-2007
  The Business Investments series documents the businesses that Taubman owned and operated, and the corporate directorships he held. This series is organized into five subseries: (a) Acquisition, Financing, and Sale Agreements, (b) Irvine Company, (c) Michigan Panthers, (d) Sotheby's, and (e) Directorships and Other Investments.
  - Acquisition, Financing, and Sale Agreements 1977-1983
    The Acquisition, Financing, and Sale Agreements subseries consists of bound volumes of legal and financial documents relating to various business investments. The volumes document Taubman's acquisition, financing, and organization of the Irvine Company; the acquisition, financing, and restructuring of Sotheby Parke Bernet Group; the acquisition of A&W Restaurants; and the acquisition of Phoenix radio stations by the Broadcast Group.
    - Irvine Company, Bank Loan Agreements, Wells Fargo Bank July 22, 1977, 3 volumes (Volume 1)
    - Irvine Company, Acquisition of 8,415,000 Shares of The Irvine Co. by Taubman-Allen-Irvine, Inc. July 22, 1977 (Volume 2)
    - Irvine Company, Organization and Capitalization of Taubman-Allen-Irvine, Inc. July 22, 1977 (Volume 3)
    - Acquisition, Financing and Reorganization of Sotheby Parke Bernet Group, p.l.c. 1983, 6 volumes (Volume 4)
    - A&W Restaurants, Inc., Acquisition by Taubman Investment Company January 1982, 2 volumes (Volume 5)
    - The Broadcast Group, Inc., Acquisition of Phoenix Radio Stations KJJJ-AM and KJJJ-FM January 1982 (Volume 6)
  - Irvine Company 1975-1985
    The Irvine Company subseries documents the 1977 acquisition of the Irvine Ranch by Taubman and his investing partners, and the management of the property from 1977 to 1983, when Taubman sold his interest. Materials include financial statements, business plans, agendas and minutes of the board of directors and committees, correspondence, clippings of news articles, and printed material, such as brochures of residential developments.
    - Board of Directors June 14, 1977 (Box 68)
    - Brochures (Box 68)
    - Clippings 1977 (Box 68)
    - Commitment Letters 1977 (Box 68)
    - Correspondence 1976-1977 (Box 68)
    - Financial Analyses (Box 68)
    - News Releases 1977 (Box 68)
    - Personnel (Box 244)
    - Press Conference (Box 68)
    - Stock Sales/Purchase Agreement (Box 68)
    - Summary of Events Leading to Purchase (Box 68)
    - Summary of Smith vs. Irvine (Box 68)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 68)
    - Reports & Correspondence 1976-1977 (Box 69)
    - Investment Property Portfolio Refinancing Summary-Owned and Managed Projects October 13, 1977 (Box 69)
    - Agriculture Division, 5-year plan November 1977 (Box 69)
    - Financial and Other Reports to Banks October 31, 1977 (Box 69)
    - Financial and Other Reports to Banks April 30, 1978 (Box 69)
    - Financial Statements for the Year Ended April 30, 1976 (Box 69)
    - Financial Statements September 30, 1979 (Box 69)
    - Irvine Company and Subsidiaries Financial Statements and Statistics Fiscal Year (for 6 months) 1975-1976 (Box 70)
    - Due Diligence Review of the Irvine Company July 20, 1977 (Box 70)
    - Business Plan (New Irvine Company) 1977 (Box 70)
    - Loan Agreement dated as of July 22, 1977, 3 folders (Box 70)
      (also includes Term Notes)
    - Prudential loan September 1977 (Box 70)
    - Parcel Review, City of Irvine, etc. (Box 70)
    - Stock Sales / Purchase Agreement (Box 70)
    - Taubman Company Report to TIAA 1976, 2 copies (Box 70)
    - Irvine Ranch Water District -- Analysis and Review (Box 70)
    - Irvine Ranch Water District -- Plans (Box 70)
    - Accounts Payable and Accounts Receivable (Box 70)
    - Consolidated Financial Statements June 30, 1982, 1981 (Box 70)
    - Miscellaneous: re. leased residential land (Box 70)
    - Shareholder's agreement (Box 70)
    - Harbor Ridge Brochures (Box 70)
    - Investment Property Portfolio (Box 71)
    - April 1976 Business Plan for the Five-Year Period Ending April 30, 1981 (Box 71)
    - April 1976 Business Plan for the Five-Year Period Ending April 30, 1981 (Box 71)
      (includes June 8, 1976 revisions)
    - April 1977 Business Plan for the Five-Year Period Ending April 30, 1982 (Box 71)
    - June 1978 Business Plan for the Five Year Period Ending June 30, 1983 (Box 71)
    - Development Strategy Parcel Review July 22, 1977, 2 copies (Box 71)
    - Lender Analysis and Review of the Irvine Company (Box 71)
    - Summary of Investigation -- TIC's General Plan for Development ("General Plan") (Box 71)
    - Detroit News Articles (Box 71)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 2 folders (Box 72)
    - Fashion Island Shopping Center, Newport Beach, 5 folders (Box 72)
    - Financial
      - Billings (Box 72)
      - Business Plan, 1 volumes; 2 folders (Box 72)
      - Compensation Study (Box 72)
      - Financial Statements / Operating Budget (Box 72)
      - Investments (Box 72)
      - Leasing Information (Box 72)
      - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 72)
      - Refinancing (Box 73)
      - Sales (Box 73)
    - Flying "D" Ranch (Box 73)
    - Ford Aeronutronic Property (Box 73)
    - Imperial Valley (Box 73)
    - Industrial (Box 73)
    - Invitations to Speak (Box 73)
    - Land Sales (Box 73)
    - Land Use (Box 73)
    - Long Range Planning (Box 73)
    - Maps (Box 73)
    - Marketing
      - General Information (Box 73)
      - Market Research (Box 73)
    - The May Company (Box 73)
    - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 73)
    - Mission Viejo Regional (Box 73)
    - Newport Center (Box 73)
    - News Articles, 7 folders (Box 73)
    - Joan Irvine Smith Correspondence
      - June 1980, 3 folders (Box 74)
      - July 1980 (Box 74)
    - Pacific Division (Box 74)
    - Partnerships (Box 74)
    - Personal Financial (Box 244)
    - Personnel
      - Executive Personnel (Box 244)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 244)
      - Plans and Benefits (Box 244)
      - Resumes (Box 244)
      - Claude Ballard (Box 244)
      - Peter C. Kremer (Box 244)
      - Richard Kughn (Box 244)
      - Joan Irvine Smith (Box 244)
    - Potential Investors (Box 75)
    - Project File (Box 75)
    - Proposed Reorganization of Company (Box 75)
    - Public Affairs, Public Relations and Governmental (Box 75)
    - Public Relations (clippings and articles) (Box 75)
    - Residential
      - Harbor Ridge (Box 75)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 75)
      - Turtle Rock (Box 75)
      - University Town Center (Box 75)
    - Speech Writers (Box 75)
    - Speeches (Box 75)
    - Stockholders (Box 75)
    - Tax (Box 75)
    - Village 14 (Box 75)
    - Water District (Box 75)
    - Woodbridge Shopping Center (Box 75)
    - Woodbridge Village Center Loan Presentation (Box 75)
    - Acquisition and Closing (Box 76)
    - Advertising/Public Relations (Box 76)
    - Agricultural (Box 76)
    - Audit Committee (Box 76)
    - Audit File #2 (Box 76)
    - Bank Accounts (Box 76)
    - Irvine Center, 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Irvine Civic Plaza (Box 76)
    - Coastal (Box 77)
    - Commercial Buildings (Box 77)
    - Contributions (Box 77)
    - Corporate: Certificate of Incorporation (Box 77)
    - Corporate Policy (Box 77)
    - Correspondence (Box 77)
    - Directors and Stockholders Meeting, 4 folders (Box 77)
    - Directors, Officers and Stockholders (Box 77)
    - Environmental (Box 77)
    - Board of Directors Agendas
      - November 14, 1977, 2 folders (Box 78)
      - Tentative February 23, 1978 (Box 78)
      - February 23, 1978 (Box 78)
      - Tentative, March 28, 1978n (Box 78)
      - March 28, 1978 (Box 78)
      - Tentative May 2, 1978 (Box 78)
      - May 2, 1978 (Box 78)
      - Tentative June 6, 1978 (Box 78)
      - Tentative August 4, 1978 (Box 79)
      - August 4, 1978 (Box 79)
      - Tentative September 11, 1978 (Box 79)
      - September 11, 1978 (Box 79)
      - Tentative October 30, 1978 (Box 79)
      - October 30, 1978 (Box 79)
      - Tentative December 4, 1978 (Box 79)
      - December 4, 1978 (Box 79)
      - Agenda and Supporting Information December 4, 1978 (Box 79)
      - January 18, 1979 (Box 79)
      - Tentative January 18, 1979 (Box 80)
      - Tentative February 25, 1979 (Box 80)
      - February 25, 1979 (Box 80)
      - Tentative March 29, 1979 (Box 80)
      - March 29, 1979 (Box 80)
      - Tentative April 30, 1979 (Box 80)
      - April 30, 1979 (Box 80)
      - Tentative August 13, 1979 (Box 80)
      - Tentative October 15, 1979 (Box 80)
      - Tentative November 12, 1979 (Box 80)
      - Tentative December 10, 1979 (Box 80)
      - Tentative June 11, 1979 (Box 81)
      - June 11, 1979 (Box 81)
      - Executive Committee July 30-31, 1979 (Box 81)
      - August 13, 1979 (Box 81)
      - September 10, 1979 (Box 81)
      - October 15, 1979 (Box 81)
      - November 12, 1979 (Box 81)
      - December 10, 1979 (Box 81)
      - Tentative January 16, 1980 (Box 81)
      - January 16, 1980 (Box 81)
      - February 19, 1980 (Box 82)
      - Tentative March 17, 1980 (Box 82)
      - March 17, 1980 (Box 82)
      - Tentative April 14, 1980 (Box 82)
      - April 14, 1980 (Box 82)
      - Tentative May 21, 1980 (Box 82)
      - May 21, 1980 (Box 82)
      - Tentative June 16, 1980 (Box 83)
      - June 16, 1980 (Box 83)
      - Tentative July 21, 1980 (Box 83)
      - July 21, 1980 (Box 83)
      - Tentative September 8, 1980 (Box 83)
      - September 8, 1980 (Box 83)
      - October 21, 1980 (Box 83)
      - November 17, 1980 (Box 83)
      - December 15, 1980 (Box 83)
      - February 16, 1981 (Box 83)
      - June 22, 1981 (Box 84)
      - January 18, 1982 (Box 84)
      - February 15, 1982 (Box 84)
      - March 22, 1982 (Box 84)
      - April 19, 1982 (Box 84)
      - May 17, 1982 (Box 84)
      - July 19, 1982 (Box 84)
      - September 13, 1982 (Box 84)
      - January 14, 1983 (Box 84)
      - March 15, 1983 (Box 84)
      - January 12, 1981 (Box 85)
      - March 23, 1981 (Box 85)
      - April 21, 1981 (Box 85)
      - May 27, 1981 (Box 85)
      - Tentative July 20, 1981 (Box 85)
      - September 14, 1981 (Box 85)
      - October 15, 1981 (Box 85)
      - Tentative November 16, 1981 (Box 85)
      - December 14, 1981 (Box 85)
    - Billings (Box 86)
    - Board Meeting and Audit Committee 1979 (Box 86)
    - Board Meeting, Detroit 1980 (Box 86)
    - Board Meeting, Detroit 1981 (Box 86)
    - Business Plans and Financial Statement 1977-1983 (Box 86)
    - Conflicts of Interest (Box 86)
    - Correspondence 1979-1981 (Box 86)
    - Correspondence and Reports 1981 (Box 86)
    - Debenture File (Box 86)
    - Memorandum of Understanding (Box 86)
    - Operating Budget and Financial Statements 1983 (Box 86)
    - Planning and Opinion Research 1977-1982 (Box 86)
    - Scott v. Irvine Company November 22, 1982 (Box 86)
    - Shareholder Agreements (Box 86)
    - Shareholder's Meeting 1980 (Box 86)
    - Speeches (Box 86)
    - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 86)
    - Financial Statements
      - March 31, 1982 (Box 87)
      - June 30, 1982 (Box 87)
      - September 30, 1982 (Box 87)
      - December 31, 1982 (Box 87)
    - Smith v. Irvine Company Pleadings, vol. 2 (Box 87)
    - Board of Directors Expense Reports 1979-1983 (Box 88)
    - Correspondence and Other Records 1977-1984, 3 folders (Box 88)
    - Irvine Deposition 1982-1985 (Box 88)
    - Litigation; Trial exhibits from The Irvine Corporation vs. Joan Irvine Smith (Box 88)
    - Litigation: Deposition of A. Alfred Taubman in the case of Peter C. Kremer vs. Donald L. Bren, Herbert Allen Sr., Newco Corp., and The Irvine Company May 4, 1984 (Box 88)